Nathaniel Mohr

18780 NW Rock Creek Cir Apt 153 Portland, OR 97229 (209) 996-8035 mohrna22@gmail.com https://nathaniel-mohr.github.io

GOALS

I am pursuing a career that would allow me to be innovative and create new things. I have an interest in analyzing and visualizing data in order to better see connections and trends that may have otherwise been missed. I also find value in creating products or processes that enhance day to day operations as well as the user experience of a product.

EDUCATION

Oregon State University, Corvallis, OR

2017 - 2021

Bachelor of Science - Computer Science

Minor in Mathematics

EXPERIENCE

Custodial Assistant

September 2019 - June 2021

Oregon State University Memorial Union

Corvallis, OR

Custodial Assistant responsible for cleaning the Memorial Union as well as the Student Experience Center, campus cultural centers, and child care building.

Intern

Clean Water Services

June 2021 - Present

Hillsboro, OR

Intern with Digital Solutions department at Clean Water Services, a water resources management utility. Developed tools and products primarily for Field Operations and Development Services departments. Worked with various servers and databases.

PROJECTS

Virtual Reality for Prototyping Factory Processes

Created a virtual reality training tool to be used with modular home development. In modular home development, pieces of the houses are built in a factory and then shipped off to the final location to be assembled on site. The goal is to allow workers to learn the stations of the factory in VR.

Augmented Reality Underground Infrastructure

Created an augmented reality app to view underground infrastructure of Clean Water Services, using ArcGIS features and Unity.

SKILLS

Programming Languages

- Bash
- C\C++\C#
- Haskell
- Java\JavaScript
- Python
- SQL

Software

- Microsoft SharePoint
- Microsoft Power BI
- Esri ArcGIS Suite

AWARDS

Eagle Scout - 2012 magna cum laude